<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Zachary Wong</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Zachary Wong</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reticulate Between R and Python</title>
      <link>/post/2020/12/07/reticulate-between-r-and-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020/12/07/reticulate-between-r-and-python/</guid>
      <description>Hello there, This is my second blog post on this project. It demonstrates the reticulate function that allows R and python to talk to each other and communicate across code chunks. I use the reticulate function on some data from my projects!
 R library(reticulate) library(readr) library(tidyverse) ## ── Attaching packages ──────────────────────────────────────────────────────────────────────── tidyverse 1.3.0 ── ## ✓ ggplot2 3.3.2 ✓ dplyr 1.0.1 ## ✓ tibble 3.0.3 ✓ stringr 1.4.0 ## ✓ tidyr 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Code and Output</title>
      <link>/post/2020/12/01/my-first-blog-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020/12/01/my-first-blog-post/</guid>
      <description>Hello there, This is my first blog post on this project. It contains python code and output.
 Python string=&amp;quot;mystring yay!&amp;quot; import re re.findall(r&amp;quot;y&amp;quot;,string) ## [&amp;#39;y&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;y&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;y&amp;#39;] import re string1=&amp;quot;We have to extract these numbers 12, 47, 48 The integers numbers are also interesting: 189 2036 314\&amp;#39;,\&amp;#39; is a separator, so please extract these numbers 125,789,1450 and also these 564,90456 We like to offer you 7890$ per month in order to complete this task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SDS 348 Project 2: Modeling, Testing, and Predicting NBA RAPTOR Scores</title>
      <link>/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project2/</guid>
      <description>By: Zachary Wong zpw97  Introduction The dataset that I chose for this project relates to the efficiency statistics of NBA players. This dataset is one of the datasets that I used for project 1, which I chose because I am a huge basketball fan and enjoy researching how players contribute to the team through their statistics. The specific dataset came from the Five Thirty Eight website, which provides many datasets related to sports, politics, economics, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SDS 348 Project 1: NBA Player Efficiency and Salaries </title>
      <link>/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project1/</guid>
      <description>By: Zachary Wong zpw97  Introduction The datasets that I chose for this project relate to NBA basketball players. I chose these because I am a huge fan of sports, especially basketball. I often find myself watching games and intensely evaluating box scores for players&#39; statistics. I find it incredibly interesting to see how players statistics (points, rebounds, assists) fluctuate over the course of the season and throughout their careers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/post/2015/07/23/hello-r-markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2015/07/23/hello-r-markdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a New Theme</title>
      <link>/post/2014/09/28/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2014/09/28/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
